https://www.pointdev.com/en/legal-forms/index.php#privacy-policy

Legal notice
OWNER POINTDEV Espace Reva 2 allee Josime MARTIN 13160 CHATEAURENARD FRANCE
Phone : 33 4 32 62 71 34
VAT number:
FR 22431638816 Web : www.pointdev.com/en/contact Email : info@pointdev.com
Technical Support Web : www.pointdev.com/en/support Email : support@pointdev.com
Personal data
In application of the law n ° 78-17 of January 6th, 1978 relative to the computing, the files and the liberties, you have the right of opposition (article 26 of the law), of access (art 34 to 38 of the law) and rectification (article 36 of the law) data concerning you.
Thus, you can demand that be rectified, completed, clarified, updated or erased information about you that are inaccurate, incomplete, equivocal, out of date or whose collection or use, communication or preservation is prohibited.
We commit ourselves to take all precautions to preserve the security of this information and in particular to prevent it from being distorted, damaged or communicated to third parties.
Privacy Policy:
We collect information when using our contact forms or account creation, in order to provide you with a commercial or technical response, following the request made. We may also collect data on your computer, browser or IP address.
All this collected data can be used to contact you, by email or phone, to respond to your request or to validate your order.
We are the only owners information collected on this site. Your personal information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to another company for any reason, without your consent, beyond what is necessary to fulfill your request.
We put implement different protection methods to ensure the security and confidentiality of your data, such as the use of an SSL certificate and the use of a secure HTTPS connection.
Only the employees concerned by your request ( sales, technical support, order and shipping service) have access to your personal data.
We use the email address you provide us to send you information about your request.
If at any time you wish to unsubscribe and no longer receive emails, detailed unsubscribe instructions are included at the bottom of each email.
Use of cookies:
For statistical and display purposes, this site uses cookies. These are small text files stored on your computer to record technical data about your navigation. In general, these cookies are used to maintain user preferences, retain shopping carts, or provide anonymous tracking data to applications such as Google Analytics. Some parts of this site can not be functional without the acceptance of cookies.
The registration of cookies requires the consent of the user and most Internet browsers are configured by default to accept cookies. You may refuse this registration at any time, but we draw your attention to the fact that the refusal of the deposit of cookies on your computer may nevertheless alter your user experience and your access to certain services or features of this website.
Each Internet browser has its own cookie management settings. To find out how to change your cookie preferences, please find below the links to help you need to access your browser's menu:
Chrome:
https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/ 95,647? hl = en
Firefox:
https://support.mozilla.org/kb/ enable-disable-cookies
Internet Explorer:
https://support.microsoft.com/fr-fr/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11
Opera:
http://help.opera.com/Windows/10.20/ en / cookies.html
Safari:
https://support.apple.com/kb/ PH21411 viewlocale = en_US & amp;? locale = en_US
Phone:
33
4 32 62 71 34
By continuing your navigation, you authorize the use of cookies for analytical purposes and functional improvement.
To revoke this consent, see our privacy policy
I accept
